Guide to the Richard C. Carroll, Assistant and Associate Dean of Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Associate Dean, Yale College, 1939-1972; Accession 1971-A-003
  - Correspondence and Subject Files, 1939-1968
    - Refrigerator (Box 36, Folder 459)
    - Registrar's Office (Box 36, Folder 460)
    - Registration (Box 36, Folder 461)
    - Registration material: freshmen, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 462)
    - Registration material: upperclassmen, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 463)
    - Reid Hall, Yale (Box 36, Folder 464)
    - Religion Department (Box 36, Folder 465)
    - Requirements, degree, etc. (Box 36, Folder 466)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps (Army and Navy) (Box 36, Folder 467)
    - Residential College System (Box 36, Folder 468)
    - Reunions (Box 36, Folder 469)
    - Rhodes Scholarship (Box 36, Folder 470)
    - Romance Languages, Dept. of (Box 36, Folder 471)
    - Rugby Club, Yale (Box 36, Folder 473)
    - "R" Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 474)
    - Scandinavian Seminar (Box 36, Folder 475)
    - Scholarship Committee H-Y-P (Box 36, Folder 476)
    - Scholarships, misc. (not Yale) (Box 36, Folder 477)
    - Schroeder Prize (Box 36, Folder 478)
    - Scientific Magazine (publication) (Box 36, Folder 479)
    - Scottish Descent Scholarship (St. Andrew's) (Box 36, Folder 480)
    - Secondary school performance at Yale (Box 36, Folder 481)
    - Seldon Prize (Box 36, Folder 482)
    - Seminars (Box 36, Folder 483)
    - Senior Advisory Board
      - 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 484)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 37, Folder 485)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 486)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 37, Folder 487)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 37, Folder 488)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 489)
    - Senior Advisory Board, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 490 - 491)
    - Senior Class Council (Box 37, Folder 492)
    - Senior Promenade class of '59 (Box 37, Folder 493)
    - Senior Prom
      - 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 494)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 495)
    - Senior Societies: above ground, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 496)
    - Senior Societies (Box 37, Folder 497)
    - Senior Societies: underground, 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 498)
    - Shoplifting (Box 37, Folder 499)
    - Singing groups (Box 37, Folder 500)
    - Soaring Club (Box 37, Folder 501)
    - Sociology: orientation survey (Box 37, Folder 502)
    - Solicitation and advertising (Box 37, Folder 503)
    - Sophomore Seminars (Box 37, Folder 504)
    - Space allocations (Box 37, Folder 505)
    - Special reading courses and tutorials (Box 37, Folder 506)
    - Special students
      - 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 507)
      - 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 508)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 509)
    - Spring vacation student trips (Box 37, Folder 510)
    - Steering Committee (Box 38, Folder 511)
    - Student Advisory Board, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 512)
    - Student agencies (Box 38, Folder 513)
    - Student Center, 1965-1967 (Box 38, Folder 514)
    - Student Conference on United States Affairs (Box 38, Folder 515)
    - Student protests (Box 38, Folder 516)
    - Student records
      - 1952-1959 (Box 38, Folder 517)
      - 1959-1961 (Box 38, Folder 518)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 519)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 520)
    - Students for a Democratic Society (Box 38, Folder 521)
    - Studies - verbal aptitudes, achievements, etc. (Box 38, Folder 522)
    - Study Abroad and in U.S. (Box 38, Folder 523)
    - Summer High School (Box 38, Folder 524)
    - Summer registration (Box 38, Folder 525)
    - Summer School transcripts (Box 38, Folder 526)
    - Summer Schools (Box 38, Folder 527)
    - Surveys (miscellaneous) (Box 38, Folder 528)
    - "S" Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 529)
    - Ten Eych Prize (Box 39, Folder 530)
    - Timothy Dwight College (Box 39, Folder 531 - 532)
    - Torch Honor Society
      - 1939-1954 (Box 39, Folder 533)
      - 1955-1962 (Box 39, Folder 534)
    - Torch Society, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 535)
    - Town and Gown (Box 39, Folder 536)
    - Town and Gown relations, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 537)
    - Transfers from Engineering (Box 39, Folder 538)
    - Travel guide (Box 39, Folder 539)
    - Trumbull College (Box 39, Folder 540)
    - Tutoring Service (general) (Box 39, Folder 541)
    - "T" Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 542)
    - Undergraduate activities, 1957-1961 (Box 39, Folder 543)
    - Undergraduate activities
      - 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 544)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 545)
    - Undergraduate activities: membership lists, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 546)
    - Undergraduate regulations (Box 40, Folder 547)
    - Undergraduate Regulations, Committee on (Box 40, Folder 548)
    - "Undergraduate Regulations" (booklet) (Box 40, Folder 549)
    - "Undergraduate Regulations": revisions, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 550)
    - University Council on Yale College (Committee) (Box 40, Folder 551)
    - USAFI Tests, 1965 July (Box 40, Folder 552)
    - Use of University Halls: general (Box 40, Folder 553)
    - Use of University Halls (Box 40, Folder 554)
    - "U" Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 555)
    - Veech, James A., Prize (Box 40, Folder 556)
    - Volunteer services (Box 41, Folder 557)
    - Volunteer services prior to 1963, Yale (Box 41, Folder 558)
    - Volunteer Services, Yale, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 559)
    - "V" Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 560)
    - Werdell '63 - Book on Student Values (Box 41, Folder 561)
    - Wiggin and Dana Law Counsel to Yale (Box 41, Folder 562)
    - Withdrawals from Yale (Box 41, Folder 563)
    - Women at Yale (Box 41, Folder 564)
    - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program (Box 41, Folder 565)
    - WYBC: general (Box 41, Folder 566)
    - WYBC
      - 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 567)
      - 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 568)
    - "W" Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 569)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine (Box 41, Folder 570)
    - Yale Club (Box 41, Folder 571)
    - Yale Co-op (Box 41, Folder 572)
    - Yale Sailing Associates (Box 42, Folder 573)
    - Yale Undergraduate (publication) (Box 42, Folder 574)
    - "Y" Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 575)
    - "Z" Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 576)
  - Carnegie Teaching Fellowships, 1957-1972
    - 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Student appraisal sheets, 1959-1960 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Expenses, 1959-1960 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Renewal application, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Expenses, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Nominations, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Student appraisal sheets, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Expenses, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Publicity (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Expenses
      - 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Expenses, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 19 - 20)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Expenses, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Duplicates and printed forms (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Records of Richard C. Carroll, Circa 1937-1961; Accession 1996-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - Army Specialized Training Reserve Program (A.S.T.P.) curriculum, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) basic academic course program (Yale and U.S. Army), Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) enrollment data, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) information bulletin corrections, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) information pamphlets, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) schedule of the Commanding Officer, July 5-9, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic failures in Yale College (1949-1950), November 20, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic predictions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic requirements amendment proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academic year report (Yale College), 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academic year reports and materials, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Activities code revisions correspondence, June 14, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Admission of women to undergraduate courses, September 28, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Admission Requirements of American Medical Colleges, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Admission to Junior year, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Admissions, 1938-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Admissions statistics, November 25, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Advanced Placement at Harvard, September 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Committee for the Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) division, third meeting summary., December 21, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni correspondence, 1949 October (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alumni sons comparison records, 1933-1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Studies (A survey of programs), September 1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Studies newsletter, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Andover and the Colleges, by Dean of Students, Benedict, G.G., April 12, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Andover Study, November 1, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Application form of McCollester, Roger S., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Approved Medical schools, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Approved schools of the basic Medical sciences, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Armed Forces Institute, June 27, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Armed Forces, reading courses proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Army Service Forces, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arnold, W. Thurman, Jr. incident, December 1940 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Attendance correspondence, December 12, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Attendence survey, February 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Aurelian committee report on extra-curricular activities, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Aurelian Honor Society report, April 1950 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Award of Alumni Fellowship, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) course of study, Yale College Committee, January 9, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) proposal of degree revisions, January 6, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bachelor of Science (B.S.) course programs correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Barber pole prank, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Basic Phase Army Specialized Training Program (A.S.T.P.) modifications, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Berkeley College, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Berzelius, 1934-1957 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Biological Science majors (1948, 1949, 1949M, 1950), 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bradner, William correspondence, October 13, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - British Schools and Colleges, Summer 1952 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - (Intra-University) Broadcasting System proposal, May 1, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Buckley, Bill; A Report by the Board of Editors of the Yale Alumni Magazine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Budget Calculations, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Campus Police correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Campus Police Department correspondence, November 14, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Campus Police, Yale, May 13, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Campus Police, Yale, January 3, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Candidate requirements for appointment as midshipman, United States (U.S.) Naval Reserve information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Candidates for the Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) degree, November 9, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Case histories, Yale class of 1941 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - CEED examination data, matriculants to the class of 1958, September 30, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Chapel talk, May 1950 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Cheating correspondence, April 4, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Cheating students statistics, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Chief elections in majors and occupations, May 8, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Chi Psi fraternity incident, February 11, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Chi Psi statistics, May 18, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Choate graduates at Yale, summary classes of 1957, 1958, 1959, September 1956 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Choate statistics, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Choate statistics, Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Choice of sophomore courses, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administration, May 16, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Civil Aeronautics Authority correspondence, August 23, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Civil Aeronautics Society memorandum to DeVane, William C., August 23, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Class and term relationships, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Class averages fall term, September 1948-February 1949 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Class list and obituary of Carroll, Clarence Franklin, 1879-1881 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Classroom absences, comparative statement of, February 24, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Classroom attendence correspondence, June 8, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Classroom attendence proposal, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Classroom attendence proposal and Dean's list rank, May 16, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Classroom attendance proposal, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Classroom attendance revised regulations, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Classroom attendance rules and correspondence, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Class statistics of 1957 and 1958, October 1955 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - (Inter) College Athletics, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - College committees list, Yale, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - College Curricular Program revision, Yale, January 12, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - College degrees to scientists starred in 1943, January 13, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - College Fellows study (fall term), 1947 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - (The) College Student, second preliminary draft, January 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Combined class statistics, Yale 1924 and 1924s (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Committee on Allocation of Students to the Colleges, March 18, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Committee on Examinations, proposed legislation on May reading period, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Committee on Fellowships, March 3, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Committee on student preparation for war service, Undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Committee on the Future of Liberal Studies, April 1943 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Committees on the Course of Study for the Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) and the Bachlor of Science (B.S.) degrees recommendations, March 20, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Committee on Distribution of Course Hours, January 5, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Comparative averages of schools sending five or more boys to Yale, first and second term, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Comparative distribution of majors, January 23, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Comparative enrollment figures, November 16, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Comparative major elections of 1950, 1951, and 1952, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Comparative Statement of Classroom Absences, February 24, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Comparative Statement of Classroom Cuts, 1938-1942 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Conference of assistant Deans, December 6 and 7, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Conference on Careers in Government, Yale, April 18 and 19, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Confidential Memorandum, The Undergraduate and the Problem of Enlistment, December 23, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Considerations on Personality Development in College Students, May 1955 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Constitutional Convention, preliminary proposals for the Yale Student Council, May 6, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - (Angelton, James Jesus) correspondence, June 11, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to Dean Carroll, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Counseling needs of students, Undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Counselor's reports, October 30, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Course changes correspondence, November 28, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Course elections tabulations (1949-1950) (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Course failures for spring term 1956, September 27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Courses in Yale College, News' Guide to, Spring 1941 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Courses of Study Committee memorandum, Undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Course of Study Committee on elections in Economics 23 and Economics 27, May 10, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Course of Study report, April 1955 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Criterion, Special Issue on Education, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Cultural Opportunities correspondence, March 12, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - The Dean and the Galloping Half-back, written by the Dean of Yale College; DeVane, William C., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - The Dean and the Psychiatrist: A Symposium, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Dean's Honor List, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Dean's office, Yale College general correspondence, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Dean's List correspondence, February 6, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Dean of Students correspondence; Carroll, Richard C., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Death warrant, November 29, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Definitive majors, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Definitive majors (class of 1951) (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Department of Health, Yale, November 22, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Detroit University School annual meeting report, May 1950 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - DeVane, William Clyde, Yale Literary Magazine, January 1941 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Dining Hall System Student Survey, Undated (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - (Yale) diploma correspondence, February 28, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Directed Studies Program survey, June 27, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Directed Studies, Sophomore Year report, July 7, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies in the departments, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Disciplinary cases and danger list, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Disestablishment of Air Force R.O.T.C. Policy, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Distributional credit rules for the class of 1959, November 8, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Distribution of Spring Term Averages, October 1, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Distribution of Student Time Informal Committee, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Distribution of Subjects and Grades on College Entrance Examinations (for the class of 1941) (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Distribution of Grades for the Departmental Examinations, June 1949 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Divisional Program in the Humanities, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Divisional Programs Advisors, Undated (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Divisional Programs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Divisional Programs observations and recommendations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Doubtful cases for graduation, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - (Timothy) Dwight College correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Eastern College Athletic Conference, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Educational Program in Yale College, Undated (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Educational Program for Members of the Armed Forces during the Period of Demobilization, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Education and American Business commencement address, June 25, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Educational Aptitude Testing in the Navy V-12 Program at Yale (preliminary report), October 12, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Education for War and Reconstruction, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Election of courses in Mathematics (Yale College), 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Election principles and procedures, February 15, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Elections to Senior Societies, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Employability of College graduates in Business and Industry, May 1944 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - End of war speech by the Dean, William C. DeVane, August 14, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Engineering School transfers correspondence, June 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - England and Wales Universities, Undated (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - English course change proposals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - English department course critique, April 1949 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - English Travelogue Excerpt, Undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Enlisted reserves registration, requirements, and proposed program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Enrollment figures, September 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Enrollment of Navy trainees at Yale, January 20, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Enrollment statistics, July 14, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Enrollment statistics, March 1946 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1948, September 30, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Enrollment statistics, September 19, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Enrollment statistics, July 31, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - (Yale) Enrollment summer statistics, April 13, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Enrollment trends, 1928-1942 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Enrollment trends, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Entering Freshmen, October 7, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Estimated majors in fall term, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Exchange of students, November 1, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Executive Committee Naval R.O.T.C. vote, May 9, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Executive Committee, Yale, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Executive Committee of Yale College, meeting minutes, June 12, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Executive Committee statistics report and class list, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Exemptions for Bachelor of Arts (B.S.) students (classes of 1950, 1950F, and 1951), January 9, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Extracurricular Yale: The Proficient Man, Undated (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Faculty chart, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Faculty Sons in Yale Classes statistics, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Failures, class of 1941 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Farewell to the Cloisters, October 31, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Fifth Annual National Conference on Higher Education, Undated (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Final Examination Legislation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Football Financial Aid Grants, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Foreign Area Studies in Yale University, Undated (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Foreign Area Studies summer reading list, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Foskett, John, December 4, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Four-course plan proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Fraternity dances, November 2, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Fraternity dances, January 12, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Fraternity statistics, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Freshmen failures by course, October 1, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Fulbright Program information, June 1956 (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Gambling syndicate incident, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General, Yale, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence from Carroll, Carl H., February 1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - General information for Miss Oliver (secretary to Mr. Carroll), Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - (Yale College) General Provisions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - General Student Conditions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Record Examination, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - General Faculty of Yale College, meeting minutes, June 13, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Grades statistics, February 7, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General warning list, October 3, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General warning list, October 12, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General warning rules and regulations, September 27, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 12)